

Beaula Ekka

Full Stack Developer | UX/UI Designer | Graphic Designer

Profile

Details

I am thrilled to embark on a new journey as a full stack developer. Drawing from my 10 years of experience as a corporate trainer, graphic designer, and IT support provider, I have honed my skills in communication, creativity, and problem-solving.

Address: Zuid Holland Netherlands By transitioning to a junior full stack developer role, I aim to leverage my previous experiences and combine them with my newfound technical skills in Full Stack development and UX/UI Design to create intuitive and visually appealing web applications.

Skills

Links

Frontend Stack Email: Beaula.favejee@outlook.com **HTML** Portfolio: https://beaula.vercel.app/ GitHub: https://github.com/BeaulaEkka CSS JavaScript Behance: https://www.behance.net/beaula

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/beaula-ekka-favejee-97316558/ TypeScript

React/ Next Vue/ Nuxt **Tailwind**

Employment History

Chakra **Graphic Designer**

GSAP Freelance, Rotterdam Area, Sep 2013 - Nov 2018

Trainer, Learning and Development

Backend Stack Node.js PHP/Laravel Python3

Automatic Data Processing, Pune, Dec 2008 - Mar 2011 Consultant Trainer Infosys, Mysore, April 2008 - Sept 2008

Sr. Executive Quality Coach/ HP Technical Support

IBM, Pune/Delhi, Jan 2005 - April 2008

Design Stack

Java

Education Photoshop

Illustrator React Native, Codecademy Feb 2024 InDesign JAVA, Codecademy Jan 2024 Lightroom PHP, Codecademy Dec 2023 XD Python 3, Codecademy, Dec 2023

Figma SQL, Datacamp, Nov 2023

Languages **English**

Frontend Software Development Winc Academy, Amsterdam, May 2023

Dutch UX/UI Design with Figma Winc Academy, Amsterdam, May 2023

Web Development Winc Academy, Amsterdam, Dec 2022

Google IT Support Professional Certification Coursera, Mar 2023

Delft University of Technology, Talen en Academische Vaardigheden, Aug 2012

Multimedia and Graphic Design Arena Multimedia, Pune, India, 2011 Technical Training, IBM, India, 2005

Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration, 2004

Southern Adventist University, Tennessee, USA off campus site: Spicer Adventist University, Pune, India